{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which circuit is known as a current-to-voltage converter?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When using an OTA in a Schmitt-trigger configuration, the trigger points are controlled by", "opta": "the Iout", "optb": "the IBIAS", "optc": "the Vout", "optd": "both Iout and IBIAS", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Refer the given circuits. Which circuit is known as an OTA?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This circuit is a setup for", "opta": "an antilog amplifier", "optb": "a constant-current source", "optc": "an instrumentation amplifier", "optd": "an isolation amplifier", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which circuit is known as a voltage-to-current converter?", "opta": "a", "optb": "b", "optc": "c", "optd": "d", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The primary function of the oscillator in an isolation amplifier is to", "opta": "convert dc to high-frequency ac", "optb": "convert dc to low-frequency ac", "optc": "rectify high-frequency ac to dc", "optd": "produce dual-polarity dc voltages for the input to the demodulator", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Refer to Figure 20-2. This circuit is a setup for", "opta": "an antilog amplifier", "optb": "a constant-current source", "optc": "an instrumentation amplifier", "optd": "an isolation amplifier", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An instrumentation amplifier has a high", "opta": "output impedance", "optb": "power gain", "optc": "CMRR", "optd": "supply voltage", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This circuit is a setup for", "opta": "an antilog amplifier", "optb": "a constant-current source", "optc": "an instrumentation amplifier", "optd": "an isolation amplifier", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Circuits that shift the dc level of a signal are called", "opta": "limiters", "optb": "clampers", "optc": "peak detectors", "optd": "dc converters", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The voltage gain of an OTA can be calculated using the formula", "opta": "", "optb": "", "optc": "", "optd": "", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In the classic three-op-amp instrumentation amplifier, the differential voltage gain is usually produced by the", "opta": "first stage", "optb": "second stage", "optc": "mismatched resistors", "optd": "output op-amp", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}